♪ In the not-too-distant
future ♪
♪ Somewhere in time and space
♪ Mike Nelson
and his robot pals ♪
♪ Are caught
in an endless chase ♪
♪ Pursued by a woman
whose name is Pearl ♪
♪ An evil gal
♪ Who wants to rule the world
♪ She threw a few things
in her purse ♪
♪ And in her rocket ship,
she hunts him ♪
♪ All across the universe
-I'll get you!
♪ I'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst I can find
♪ La-la-la
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And I'll monitor his mind
♪ La-la-la
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La-la-la
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
-Robot roll call!
-Cambot!
-You're on.
-Gypsy!
-Oh, my stars!
-Tom Servo!
-Check me out!
-Crow!
-I'm different.
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts
♪ La-la-la
♪ Just repeat to yourself
♪ It's just a show,
I should really just relax ♪
♪ For "Mystery Science Theater
3000." ♪
[Doors thud and creak]
[Doors whir]
[Doors thud and clank]
[Door slams]
-Well, hi, everyone.
Welcome to the Satellite of
Love.
♪ Here we come a-wassailing
♪ Et cetera
Et cetera ♪
-Give us our wassail if you
please, sir.
-Uh, wassail?
I'm pretty sure I'm fresh out ofwassail.
-You're no fun.
Man.
-Well, come on.
It's July.
-I know, but where's the
challenge in wassailing
at Christmas?The place is lousy with wassail.
Take two steps, and bam!
You smash your toe on tons
of the lousy stuff.
-Wait, wait, wait a minute.
What is wassail anyway?
-Oh, um, well, uh...
-It's, you know -- It's, uh...
-I don't know.
I think it's an
anti-inflammatory or something,
but the point is, if you can'tprovide wassail for wee, humble,
tattered minstrels, you got to
turn over your debit card
and pin number immediately.
-Yeah, it's a custom that goes
back centuries.
-You made that up.
-Nuh-uh.
Listen to the song.
♪ If the person
who you sing to ♪
♪ Can't provide the wassail
♪ You are entitled to his debit
card and pin number ♪
♪ Love and joy come to you
♪ Unless you can't provide the
wassail ♪
-We'll be right back.
♪ Then severe
financial penalty ♪
♪ Shall come to you
♪ Then severe financial
penalties to you ♪
♪♪
-Okay, that's the Smurf brooch
with the Diamonelles,
the porcelain cat, and I think
I'd like to order a...
-Hold on. Hold on.
Hold on. Hold on.
I have wassail.
-Hold on there, Nelson.
Canned wassail?
-No way, my friend.
- Oh, yeah.
I checked the lyrics to your
dumb little song,
and it doesn't say anything
about canned wassail.
-Wait, let me see that there.
♪ To have the party
of the first ♪
Damn, he's right!
-Nelson, you found a loophole,
you rat.
-Hold everything.
The castle is calling, and
something is wrong.
-Oh, you bet there's something
wrong!
The Lawgiver went on vacation
and left us with a babysitter.
Look!
-Why won't you play with the
blocks?
-I don't want to play with
blocks.
It's insulting.
I have an infinite intellect.
-I think you're a little crabby,
and you might need a time-out tothink about it.
-No, I can't stand time-outs,
the silence, the desolation!
-Okay, are you going to play
nice with the blocks?
-All right, Steffi.
You win this time.
-You see?
It's horrible, and she calls me
Fluffykinz
and treats me like an animal.
-Hey, did you chew this?
-Um, yes.
-No!
No chew!
No!
God, man, there's hair
everywhere.
-Please don't treat me like
this.
I'm a distinguished professor ofanthropology
from the future where apes
evolved from men.
-No chew!
No!
Go lie down.
-Oh, okay!
-Okay, which one of you is Mike?
-Uh, that would be me.
Hi.
- Okay, and which one of you is
Servo,
and which one of you is Cow?
-Um, I'm Servo.
-And I'm Cow.
-Crow.
-What?
-You're Crow.
-Yeah, I know.
Well, of course, I'm Crow.
I just said I'm Crow,
you great feeb.
-But she...
-Boy.
-Never mind.
He's Crow.
-Well, now it says here I'm
supposed to send you a movie.
Right?
-Um, excuse me, Steffi.
-Yes, Brian.
-No, it's Brain -- I mean, BrainGuy --
I mean, Observer --
Oh, never mind.
I'm finished, and I'm going to
my room to commune
with the Gossabanauthics of the
plangent dimension.
-Well, it's 4:00.
It says you take your fruit
snack at 4:00.
-I don't need to take my fruit
snack,
but I will because I want to.
Thank you.
-Okay, guys, your movie is
called "The Touch of Satan."
Ugh.
And you -- you need
another tick bath.
-No, no.
[Howling]
-Enjoy the great taste of
wassail...
-Mm.
-...in cans.
-Hey, that's ours!
-Come on, you big lush.
-Oh, it's Movie Sign.
-We got Movie Sign.
-Mm.
-You know, that is our wassail.
We worked hard for that.
-You know what, guys, I don't
even think you'd like it.
It's kind of skunky.
-Well, check the freshness date
on it.
-Yeah, let me see here.
Oh, well, there's the problem.
It says 1547.
-Yeah, that's a pretty old
born-on date.
-Yep.
-Mm, need to give that ugly guy
a call.
Huh?
-Uh...
You know, I hope the whole movie
isn't lit by a hurricane
lantern.
-Oh!
That dirt hill is getting worse
every time.
-I hear you, man.
Moo.
Let me tell you.
-Come on, girl.
Don't stop now.
I've already missed my TV.
-Yeah, I don't care
if you're scared.
You can't sleep in the house.
- Whoa.
Whoa.
Look out, you guys!
Look out!
Duck!
- Ow.
-Oh, no.
Come on.
-Ow.
-Ooh, I must be getting old.
-Why won't you lay any eggs?
-Mercy, if you'd come in
like the rest of them...
-Mercy?
-...there wouldn't be
all of this chasing.
-Yeah, milk me.
-Oh, I can tell by the look
in your eye that you like
all of the fussing.
Well, just stand there
like a good girl.
-Hello, tractor.
How are you this evening?
-Well, hello, pile of dung.
-Now what did I do
with that darn pitchfork?
-Maybe the dadblagit thing
is over yonder.
-I know I left it
in here someplace.
[Cat meows]
All right.
Who's in here?
-Oh, there's my
Walk-Me-Wet Miss Susan.
-Is that you, Robert?
-Robert the Cat.
-You're supposed to be in bed,
you little rascal.
-With Andrew the Dog.
-Now, wherever you are,
you better come out here.
-When sore throat pain strikes.
-The American Gothic people
take revenge.
♪♪
-And then he died.
-I shouldn't laugh about it.
He might've been hurt.
-Nah, he's a rock.
-Ah, I'll get more fresh blood.
-Anybody want any more coffee?
-[Mumbling]
-I'll heat it up.
-No, thanks, not for me.
I'm goin' in to watch the late
news and go to bed.
-Me either.
-It's open!
-What is that racket?
What's going on out there?
-Grandma Kramer.
-Lucinda, get her in here!
-Oh, my God.
What is it?
What's the matter?
-A kabuki actor has been hit.
-Come on, Grandma
Dried Apple Head.
-What happened?
What have you done?
-It'll be all right.
-I stayed in the tanning booth
for a whole decade!
-Stop it.
-Oh, look at the blood.
-Oh.
-From now on,
take your bloody clothes
off on the porch, please.
-The last days of Edgar Winter.
-She's done it again.
-Oh, we don't know.
-Don't we?
-Eleven years.
-And before that nine
and before that and...
-Oh, please, Melissa.
-Farmer square head.
-I've got to do something.This torment can't last forever.
-You know that it can.
-No, there's a way.
-Right after this.
-Ah, "The Touch of Satan"
softens your hands
while you do the dishes.
-This is very '70s.
I'm guessing Anthony Zerbe
must be in this.
-No, you know, I think it's
Tony Musante as a kind of hip
Satan who solves crimes.
-Could be.
-Emby Mellay?
That's not a name.
That's a bad Scrabble hand.
-With Screwtape on kettle drum!
Wormwood on harpsichord!
♪♪
-Okay, Crow, I'm putting you
on Clu Gulager alert.
-I'm on it, Mike.
I take this very seriously.
-All right.
♪♪
Oh, David Spade is Satan.
-That's good casting.
-Oh.
-The vineyards of Ernest
and Julio Satan.
-Ha, right.
Well, you know he's Satan
because he didn't signal
his turn.
-Boy.
-Spreading evil and hay fever
wherever he goes.
♪ When there's just a touch
of Satan in your heart ♪
♪♪
-He drives a Maverick.
You know,
I would have put the prince
of darkness in a muscle car.
-Hmm.
♪♪
♪ What do you get when you fall
from grace ♪
♪ You only get cast
into perdition ♪
-Good.
♪♪
-There he goes.
So long, foul deceiver.
-Bon voyage,
onerous spinner of lies.
-Hasta luego,
Maverick-driving Kludde!
-Ye --Kludde?
-Kludde?
-Yeah, it's Scottish.
I looked it up.
-Huh, okay.
-I did.
-Odd, disturbing score
co-written by Mike Post
and Igor Stravinsky.
-Sight see on your own
time, Beelzebub!
-Honk, honk, get off the road,
man-goat!
-Satan's harmonica band
led by Toots Thielemans.
♪♪
-Well, he is the master
of torture.
He would have really
long credits like this.
-Mm-hmm.
-Mike, behind that tree,
it's Clu Gulager!
-Where?
-Oh, shoot.
It was Monte Markham.
I should resign my post.
I'm just not doing a good job.
-Thanks anyway.
Appreciate it.
-Thanks.
♪♪
-I should phone Satan,
tell him I'm going to be
just a little late.
-Hmm, what was Anne Heche
doing in there?
-Citizen's arrest!
Oh, wait, I'm a cop.
-Ugh, just taking a breather
here.
I get really winded.
Ooh.
-Nice-looking town
you got here.
-You can't pay, can you?
-Yeah, well, don't let
that fool you none.
More going on here
than meets the eye.
-No kidding.
Like what?
-Well, look what I'm doing
to your car.
-Like murder,
brother, like murder.
-Murder?
-Yes sirree bub.
A farmer down the road
got killed in his barn
by a pitchfork, happened
a little over a week ago.
-They catch the guy yet?
-No, I'm still at large.
-Nope, my money
they won't either.
That'll be $6 even.
-Oh, and an extra dollar
for the aliens in my head.
-See, the way I got it figured,
this job was done by one
of them fromachidal maniacs.
-Ah.
-And we ain't gone none of them
around here.
Stamps?
-Uh, no thanks.
-Back rub?
-Oh, come on.
-Yep, long gone by now.
They won't catch him
until he kills again.
-Being him, I should know.
-You're right.
Nobody needs --
uh, what did you call it?
-What the hell is he doing?
-A fromachidal maniac.
-It's even funnier this time!
-Yeah, well, nobody needs
a fromachidal maniac
hanging around.
-Is that right?
I should check my dictionotomy.
-What with all these gas
crises and Watergates,
I needed a good laugh.
[Chuckling]
♪♪
-Hey, wait a minute.
The gas station guy
forgot to give me
my Roman Gabriel cocktail glass.
-Oh, no, the credits are going
to unspool backwards now.
♪♪
-Looks like a nice private placeto practice streaking.
-Weren't they concerned about
holding an audience
back in the '70s at all?
I mean...
-No, no.
Back then, talkies were
still a novelty.
-Oh.
♪ Doom da dum dum dum
You know, I was just thinking,
and that Gerald Ford
is rather clumsy.
♪♪
-Thank you, Lurch.
-I'm going to get out my guitar
and practice
"Sister Golden Hair."
-Wow, I'm the first one
at the Rainbow Gathering.
♪♪
♪ But the trees can't help
their feeling ♪
♪ If they like the way
they're made ♪
-Mike, stop it now!
-Sorry.
-It's the first Richard
Carpenter music video.
♪♪
-Well, this is not putting me
in mind of Satan here.
Believe me.
It's pretty easy to put me
in mind of Satan.
-Yeah, tell me about it.
♪♪
-Heh, let's see Christopher
Atkins skip a stone like that!
-Ow.
-You can't eat ham
just anywhere.
You got to find
just the right place.
-Ah, right next
to the dead raccoon.
-Oliver Hardy, just eat!
-Oops, sitting in the water,
that was real easy to avoid.
-I'm not going back, Jim.
-I'm worried that my sandwich
may be small and inadequate.
-What's on the spit, pilgrim?
Heh-heh
-Okay, you sellingHerbal Essences or Irish Spring?
-This your pond?
-You can, uh, take your time.
It's a tough question.
-Belongs to my father.
-Oh, does your father mind
if people skip rocks
across his pond?
-Just don't hit
his favorite frog.
-I don't think he's ever
mentioned it.
-Oh.
Do you want half a sandwich?
-No, but don't let me stop you.
-Just ram that moldy olive loaf
into your loser face.
-That your car?
-Mm-hmm.
-Mind if I skip
rocks across it?
-Pretty car.
-Thanks.
-Huh.
-Well, I suppose the plot
is not going to unfold itself.
-Yep.
-What's your name?
-Melissa Strickland.
-Mine is Jody,
Jody Lee Thompson.
Only I don't care
for the Lee very much.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Uh, are we starting over?
-Want half a Mr. Pibbs?
-What are you doing down
by our pond, Jody?
-Mellowing out.
-Lunch.
-You on a journey?
-Yes, I guess so.
I'm not going any place special.
-Just drove through
some credits.
That was fun.
-Yeah, keep on trucking,
I guess.
I guess you'll do your thing,
and I'll do mine.
Yep, Whip Inflation Now.
Bye.
-You're pretty,
you know that?
-Sort of a floppy Rhoda way,
I guess.
-Yes, I guess so.
-I bet you have
nine boyfriends.
-No.
-Six.
-Three.
-None.
-Two.
Let me change my answer!
-You're putting me on.
How come?
-Well, it's just that we live
on a farm.
-We don't raise boyfriends.
-It's none of my business
anyway.
What kind of a farm?
-We grow walnuts mostly.
-Walnuts, huh?
I've never been
on a walnut ranch.
-How many head of walnut
do you have?
-Can you meet my needs please?
-What's the matter?
-My prize walnut died.
-Nothing.
I was just wondering, would you
like to come up and see it?
-Uh-oh.
-The ranch?
Why?
-Well, you said you'd
never been on one...
-Smooth.
-...and since you're not going
any place special.
-Add to my general fund
of knowledge.
Well, will you give me a walnut?
-Yes, maybe two.
-Well, you can't beat that.
Let's go.
-You can help me calve a walnut
if you're lucky.
-Man, if she doesn't love him
after riding in his Maverick,
she's a total ice princess.
-Yep.
-Surprisingly short run-on time
for a '70s car.
[Rooster crows]
-You catch Kotter last night?
-Mother!
-He's the best I could do.
-This is Jody.
-Hello.
-He's just
passing through, Mama.
-Hello, Jody.
-Or should I call you Buffy?
-Supper will be ready directly.
You look like you could do
with something
besides a chili dog
for a change.
-Well, you're right about that.
-Sit right over there.
-Thank you.
-Melissa, go get your father
and tell him,
"We've got company."
-So can you tell me how to get
your daughter in the sack?
-She's a pretty girl,
isn't she?
-Yes, ma'am.
She is.
-Yeah, I can't imagine
where she got it.
-Where'd she find you?
-Down by the pond.
-By the pond?
-Hmm?
-Those walnuts are tearing
through the hay.
-What is it?
-We have company for supper.
-Company, who?
-Nobody you know, just a boy
I met down by the pond.
-A boy you met?
You brought him to the house?
-Yes, I did.
He's nice.
I just want to talk to him.
That's all.
-I mean, I might
kill him, but...
-Melissa, you don't
have the right.
-The right?
The right to what,
to talk to someone?
Now don't get so excited.
He's just passing through.
He'll be gone soon.
-Is that all there is to it?
Is it?
You didn't call him,
did you?
-Or mail anything?
-No.
I tell you, it's all right.
-What about Lucinda?
-She can eat in her room.
Now come on up to the house.
-Or you're grounded, Dad.
-Herbert von Karajan
is not pleased with that.
-And be nice to him.
-So, you're just
passing through?
-Yes, ma'am.
-I'm just going to take
some of this stuff with me.
I'm setting up a new apartment.
-All right.
Where's the idiot?
-Daddy, this is Jody Thompson.
-This is my unbelievably
sweaty dad.
-Hello, Jody.
-How's Uncle Bill?
-How do you do?
-You hungry?
I could eat a horse.
-Yeah, I guess I could too.
-Good.
Have a drink, young man.
-Now, Jody, there won't be
any hard feelings
if you don't want any of that.
-Oh, bosh.
-Oh, Hieronymus.
-He'll love this stuff.
Best darn cider in the whole
country, I make it myself.
I, uh, put peanuts in it...
-Ooh, I sure hope
he said peanuts.
-...brings out the taste.
-You know, with Mitchum,
you can skip a week.
Did you know that?
-Well, to BO!
-Man, that's good!
Mm!
-Tastes vaguely of back sweat.
-Supper ready?
-Just about.
Wash up, everybody.
[Doors closing]
♪ Everybody is working
for the weekend ♪
-Whoa.
Holy cow.
Whew.
-What's up, Mike?
-Decided to start
a walnut ranch
like that guy in the film there.
Man, is that hard work.
-Hey, I hear you.
-Whew, man, barely got started
and look at me.
-Hey, you look like hell.
-Oh, yeah.
I know, and I was just leafing
through the catalogs.
How do you account for that?
-Well, it's darn hard work,
my friend.
-Man, you said it.
Oh, I'm not going to make fun
of walnut ranchers anymore.
I'll tell you that.
-No.
♪ Doo do doo boom boom
♪ Ba boom boom boom
-Oh, Mike, you been walnut
ranching or something?
-Yeah. Look at me.
I'm just ragged.
-Yeah, well, I could've
told you that, man.
Me, I've been pecan farming.
It's like rolling off a log.
Just made my first million, too.
Haven't even grown
a single pecan.
-We'll be right back.
-Mike, could you back off?
You smell like canned tamales.
-Oh, yeah, I'm sorry.
Ugh!
♪♪
-Tell me, Jody,
you think you'll ever stop...
-It's a bit gamy there.
-...bumming around?
-Sure, I will, Mr. Strickland,
as soon as the excitement
wears off
or I find something
I really want.
-He wants my hair,
doesn't he?
-You know, I gave a lot ofthought to this before I did it.
I just didn't jump up and run.
-Well, sounds like you know
what you're about, son.
-I don't actually.
How'd you pick that up?
-How about another little drink
of my cider?
-No, thank you.
Besides, I've got
to get back on the road.
-No, why don't you wait
until morning?
The highway is going
to be foggy tonight.
-Melissa, if Jody
wants to leave,
we really shouldn't
try to keep him.
-Yes, Melissa, if he has
to get to San Francisco...
-Well, I'm in no hurry.
I just don't want to strain
your hospitality.
-Don't be silly.
It's no strain, and besides,
we've got a spare room.
You can be off first thing
in the morning.
-I just mopped up the blood
from the last guy.
-Well, I'd hate to be
any more trouble.
-Well, you are.
-It's no trouble at all.
-To kill you.
-Is it, Mother?
-No, I'll just tell
Leatherface you're here.
-Of course not.
I'll fix up the sewing room.
-The sawing room!
-I'll go with you in case
you need any help.
-Should we have Jody
as our guest,
or should I just drill
right into my molar?
-I sure appreciate it.
-Don't say anything
more about it.
You and I can pick up
the dishes,
and then we'll go for a walk.
-We pick them up for a second
and set them down.
It's an odd custom.
-Do you like living out here
like this in the country?
-I suppose so.
It's the only way
I've ever lived.
-Didn't you ever want
to do something different?
-Like what?
-Oh, I don't know,
just something different.
-Not everyone can be
like you, you know?
You're lucky.
-Your death will be quick.
-Yeah.
Yeah, I guess I am.
-But you get to watch
the walnuts
grow up wild and free.
-What's it like?
-What?
-The steering on your Maverick.
-Being able to do exactly whatyou want to do every single day.
-It's exciting.
-Exciting?
-Exciting.
-Yes.
Why do you think I turned down
your road today?
-Why did you?
-Because I wanted to see
what was at the other end.
-And your end was
at the other end.
-And I got lucky
because you were there.
-Help, please!
Please!
♪♪
-Huh, girls usually run
a lot farther away from me.
♪♪
-This is where the fish lives.
-Why did you run?
-Because this is where
the fish lives.
-Felt like it.
I really wanted to fly, but I
couldn't do that, so I ran.
-You're kind of an idiot,
aren't you?
-This is where my tongue lives.
-Please, not in front
of the fish.
-Um, he -- hey, your hoof is
on my sneaker.
-Mm, that was really bad.
-Tell me about yourself,
who you are, all of that.
-Where your fish lives.
-Well, my father
is a Russian count,
and when the Bolsheviks came...
-Stop it.
-You don't believe that?
-No.
-Well, it could be true.
-Stop it.
-Oh, sure, Miss This Is
Where The Fish Lives.
-Okay.
My father is a lawyer.
-For the Czars' court.
-And he wants me
to be a lawyer, too.
-Stop it.
-I told him, I didn't know yet,
that I wanted to go out and pokearound the country for a while.
-Stop it.
-So he gave me the car, $300
and a handshake, and here I am.
-Stop it.
-Do you let him know
what you're doing?
-Sure, I do.
I think he'd like to be with me.-Stop it.
-He sounds like a nice man.
-Yes, he's a very nice man.
-Really crooked lawyer though.
Man, he'll embezzle the socks
right off you.
-Hallmark Hall of Fame presents
"The Touch of Satan."
♪ Come sit with me
and Satan too ♪
♪ He's your friend and mine
-You know, I like you.
I did right away.
-Like most women.
-You like me too, don't you?
Don't you?
-Uh-huh.
-In a Ron Palillo
sort of way, sure.
-Funny, isn't it?
I wonder what causes a thing
like that.
-Maybe I hexed you.
-You mean,
put the whammy on me?
-Maybe.
-Nope, not me.
-I already had the whammy
when I was little.
-Will you stay here a few days?
-By this log, and don't move.
-Huh?
-Stay here with me.
-What?
-Stay here.
-Huh?
-Stay here!
-Well...
-I'm lonely, Jody.
I need someone to talk to,
to share things with,
just for a few days.
-Someone to share
clunky dialogue with.
-Well, I was going to be
in San Fran...
-Cisco?
-Well, what about your folks?
-I already live with them.
-Oh, Jody.
-You're such an imbecile.
-You know what I mean,
would they mind?
-No.
-All right.
-I'll leave.
-Mm.
-Oh, do you know how long it's
been since I've felt this good?
-Must be at least 50 years.
-No, since the last guy left,
about a week ago.
-Oh, now he's rubbing his Ryan
O'Neal-y face all over hers.
-Yeesh.
-Ugh.
Ugh.
-Let's get up, first thing
in the morning.
We can have
the whole day together.
-I'll wear my goat's head.
It'll be fun.
-What's so funny?
-You.
You are.
Come on.
Let's go.
-Put on the gloves.
Go six rounds.
See what you're made of.
Come on.
Let's go.
-Night, fish.
-Goodnight, kid, glub, glub.
♪♪
-Uh, just want to drive
through the director
of photography credit
real quick.
-Instant ball and chain,
I tell you.
-Great "Bold Ones" tonight,
huh, honey?
-Did you have a nice walk?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Um, don't come up for about
5 minutes, okay.
-Good night.
-I sure love
the yelling channel.
-Huh, your folks seem
nice and evil.
-That's your room.
-There's ton of varnished bread
laying around in there.
Just push it out of the way.
-Huh, nice door.
I'd like to see it crumpled up
next to my bed... Oh, wait.
-Bang on my door
in the morning?
-At 6:00?
-Sure, why not.
-Okay.
-We'll have to get up
and milk the walnuts.
-Hmm.
-Good night, creepy,
vacuous girl.
-Uh, so I don't need
a kiss or anything.
I'm fine.
[Door closes]
-[Humming]
-I like to sniff my blinds
before I go to bed.
-Hey, Beelzebub,
Kali, and Lucifer!
-Huh.
-Hey, a signed copy
of the Necronomicon here.
-"You guys scare me,
ha, ha, ha.
Signed, Satan."
-Ah! Its a hideous thing
made of skin!
Oh, it's just me.
-Ah, that represents
all my hang-ups, man,
and I just let them fall.
Cool.
-Huh.
-Hmm.
-Uh, excuse me,
I think I left a Sustacal back
in the corner there.
-Go away.
-Who are you?
-My name is
Margaret Rawhide-Chew.
-Go!
-Hmm.
-I usually like the left side
of the bed if that's okay.
-Huh.
Did a plucked turkey
in a wig just talk to me?
-Uh, front desk?
There's a mummy in my room.
-Uh, Mrs. Rotting-Pumpkinhead?
Hello?
-Who is it?
-It's me.
-Is Captain Hook there?
-I've got to talk to you.
-Do you have a needle?
I need to reinflate
your grandma.
-What's the matter?
-Is there anybody else in this
house that I don't know about?
-Well, you know about
Mrs. Wilma Failed-Genetic-
Experiment, right?
-Lucinda.
-She came right in my room
and scared the hell out of me.
-I'm sorry she frightened
you, Jody.
-She only kills
when she's crazy.
-But you mustn't pay
any attention to her.
She's an old woman,
and she likes to wander
around the house.
It won't happen again.
-Who is she?
-She's my great-grandmother.
-She's not that great.
-What happened to her face?
-She was badly burned
when she was a young girl.
That's why she doesn't go out
very much because of her face.
-Unless she's got
a coffee coupon.
-Go back to bed.
She was just curious.
I'll go talk to her.
-Okay.
-Oh, and there's a huge,
insane,
scabby gorilla
wandering around too.
-Why did she say go away?
-She's afraid of strangers.
-Well, she wasn't afraid
to come into my room
without knocking.
-She's an old lady, Jody!
-They don't know what they're
doing half the time.
-I tell you what,
I'll go flip her left
turn signal on, and she'll
go right back to sleep.
-I -- I'm sorry.
Go back to bed.
-Uh, could you make
your grandma wear a bell?
-Okay.
♪♪
-I'm going to
lock the door now.
Do you understand?
-I haven't understood anything
since McKinley went down.
-[Mumbling]
-Uh, she's saying never try
to deep-fry a snowball.
-No.
It's late.
-Huh.
-You have to go to sleep now.
Tomorrow I'll take you
for an extra long walk.
-All the way to the dressing
table and back.
-[Mumbling]
-You know, there's a delightful
scene later in the movie
where this old woman raps.
-Wow.
-No, there isn't.
-Good night...
-And by "Good night"
I mean, "Shut up."
-...my sister.
-Oh, I just wanted to give
her a Werther's.
-Oh, man.
Now a withered, old Billy Zane
is going to come in
and give her a withered old
coeur de la mer.
-Yeah.
-Ah, good day.
Took a walk.
Got that dress sewn.
Killed.
-Ah, a wrinkle!
-Ooh!
Oh, it's kind of a lateral move,actually.
-She turned into
Cecilia Bartoli.
-Huh.
-I miss my Eddie Munster
widow's peak.
♪♪
-I've still got to work
on the mustache, though.
-Ah, back to being
Swifty Lazar.
-Hmm.
-Who's got it going on?
Me!
That's who!
-What else are we going
to do today, hmm?
-Well, would you mind
driving me to town
so I can go to the store?
-Sure.
-Ow, my pet tick!
-I'll go change and tell them
we're leaving.
Meet me at the car.
-Okay.
-Hey, I got rooked.
-The cup is glued to my lip.
-The mom looks like Ron Popeil.
She does.
-I asked Jody
to stay a few days,
and he agreed.
-He agreed that she asked him?
-Figured you would.
-Jody is going to drive me
to the store.
-Does she know
everything we need?
-Yes.
-We'll probably stop by where
the fish lives.
-I said Jody has agreed
to stay a few days.
-We heard you the first time.
-We weren't interested
then either.
-And it's all right with you?
-No, it's not all right
with me,
but it's your decision,
not mine.
-Uh, Mike, if you're ever
this family's secret Santa,
don't buy them pot holders.
-That means a great deal
to me, Luther.
-I mean, Mr. Vandross.
[Rooster crows]
-Thank you.
♪ Is this the little demon
I carried ♪
-Go to the store.
-Buy canned peaches
and dishwashing liquid.
-I should stop
dying my eyebrows.
-Melissa.
-Hmm?
-What are you going
to tell him?
-I don't know.
I'll have to wait and see.
[Footsteps]
-Are they miking her
shoe bottoms?
-Well, time to stick my cup
back on my lips.
[Rooster crows]
-Oh, yeah.
He's a hot one, all right.
-Oh, and they don't need plant
holders either, Mike.
I mean, you know,
if you're their secret Santa.
-Got it.
-Well, off
to my stewardess job.
-Ready to go?
-Yes.
Let's go.
-Take a left.
Right there.
Good.
♪♪
-Look out!
Walnut stampede!
-Hey, want to play
pitchfork bug?
-Well, now, Andy, I think
there was a demon in the car!
-Ooh.
-Enhance your moody soundtrack
music with tiny fart sounds!
-He's got two huge Sudafed
on top of his car.
See?
Pfft, pfft, pfft, pfft.
-Huh.
From the waist down, a woman.
-Man, I try to keep fit, but
after the third baby, you know.
[Doorbell rings]
-Um, hi.
Have you seen
the other Village People?
-Boy, that body pile is really
growing.
Oh, that Grandma.
-Die, die, die!
I mean, hello.
-Well, hello, Mr. Mason.
-Howdy, Mrs. Strickland.
Luther around?
-I believe he's
around the back.
-You mind if I wander
back there?
-Of course not.
-Thank you, ma'am.
-Just got a real walnut jones
today, ma'am.
-There's not anything wrong,
I hope.
-Oh, no, Mrs. Strickland.
I just want to chew the fat
with Luther for a while.
I'll be seeing you.
-He even brought his own fat.
-Ew.
-Hmm.
Would he even fit
in the iron maiden?
-Well, hello, John.
What brings you out this way?
-And if you say "My squad car,"
I'll chainsaw you in half.
-Oh, nothing much.
Just kind of poking around.
-Sit down.
Take a load off.
-Thank you.
-Got the kettle of hands going,
I see.
-Luther, doesn't the back
of your place butt up
against
old man Larson's property?
-It sure does.
-You don't mind if I chew
on this stick insect, do you?
-You still working on
that Larson business?
-Harris Townley has still got
his wind up.
-Ooh.
-He thinks if we can
break this thing,
he'll be re-elected sheriff for
the next 20 years, damn fool.
He's running around over
in Newport
like he thought
he was J. Edgar Hoover.
-Pretty dress, though.
-How can I help?
-Do you mind if I just take
a look around your place?
-Of course not.
What are you looking for?
-Hell, I don't know.
We ain't found nothing yet.
Not even a suspicious
looking cow chip.
-Hmm.
-Looks like whoever killed
the old man
went up in a puff of smoke.
-I see.
So you don't have any ideaat all who might have done this.
-Nope.
Nothing.
That's why we're all
just out poking around.
I guess the sheriff hopes
we'll find a signed confession
just laying in the grass.
-Well, help yourself
to my place, John.
Take all the time you want.
-Just don't spook the walnuts.
-Thanks a lot, Luther.
I appreciate that.
-Listen...
-My tummy is growling.
-You get through poking around,
come on up to the house, and
we'll have a touch of my cider.
-I knew you were going to
say that, Luther.
-Then give me the finger
like that.
-But if Sheriff Townley
finds out
I was drinking your cider,
I may have to start
working for a living.
Thanks anyway, Luther.
I'll see you in town.
-Uh, by the way,
there's no reason to look
in the crawl space.
Heh-heh.
-She's going to go buy
a whole bunch
of Procter & Gamble products.
-Why do I suddenly feel hungry
for Carnation Ice Cream?
-I like this place because
they have bulk eye of newt.
-Two, three!
-And then, get this, four!
-Morning, Mr. Gentry.
-Oh, Melissa.
-Please feel free to peruse
my supply of unguents,
suspensions, tinctures,
compounded formulas,
and other sundries.
-Huh.
Anyway, I will shake the paint
off your walls, honey.
-What's the matter
with these people?
You'd think we had
the plague or something.
-It's not you, just me.
-Yep, got the plague.
Want to make out?
-They always behave that way.
-Well, why?
-They say in this town
that I'm a witch.
-A witch?
-It only rhymes with witch.
-Ah, you
plague-ridden little witch!
-Here.
-Ah.
-See what I mean?
-Witches can't lift flour
on their own.
-Why do they think
you're a witch?
-Because I am.
-Oh, stop it.
-You don't believe me?
Ask them.
-She gives them 15.55
just so she can get
6.66 back in change.
-This is a tense moment because
she used to date the grocer.
-Ah.
-Thank you, Melissa.
-You're welcome.
-Then you'll just deliver
the broomsticks to my house?
-Hey, they got a sale
on mismatched beer!
-Hmm.
-Steinlager, Pete's.
-Zah!
-Ah, you made me go burpy.
-Heh, heh, I said "zah."
-Young whipper-snapper.
-Where's he from?
-The grocer's wife died
when someone said "zah."
It's not funny.
-Why did you do that?
-Serves them right.
-You just made it worse doing
a silly thing like that.
-I'm sorry, Melissa,
but that sort of thing bugs me.
-Come on.
Let's go.
-I've said "zah" in better
towns than this.
-After the movie,
remember to pick up
some Carnation Ice Cream!
♪♪
-Okay.
Here we go.
Anything?
-Hmm.
Hmm.
Nope.
Nope, nope, I'm fine, Mike.
I guess all we can do
is add more rocks.
-Okay.
-You know, I'm worried.
If I wasn't a witch, I'd be deadby now or at least shrieking
out a confessions or raining
down curses on my tormentors,
but instead, hey, I'm great.
I couldn't be better.
-Okay.
Anything?
-Oh, no.
Did you actually add one?
No, I'm fine.
Very comfortable, in fact.
I can't believe this!
-Yeah, Crow, what I don't get
is why do you assume you're
a witch in the first place.
-Well, I --
I don't really assume it, Mike,
but I guess it's always been in
the back of my mind, you know?
-Hmm, yeah, but you know, Crow,
the reason you can survive
all of this
is because of
your durable molybdenum frame.
-Well, that's nice of you
to say, Mike,
but let's face it,
I'm a witch!
You might as well burn me
at the stake.
-Crow, you're not a witch,
but, you know, it is hard for meto prove a negative, you know?
I can't really proveyou're not a frog, for instance.
-Uh! Mike, this is weird.
-Oh, what?
Are --are you feeling
some pain?
Is it working?
-No, how did you know
I was thinking
I might be a frog?
Did I tell you that?
-No, I mean, I just used it
as an example, I...
-Ribbit.
I'm a frog!
Ribbit.
Get these rocks off me.
I can't stand
this kind of weight!
I'm a tiny frog!
-No, you're not a frog!
[Alarm blaring]
-Hey, you guys,
we got Movie Sign!
-Ribbit.
-Oh, well, help with this rock.
-Okay.
-Whoa!
-You know what this mean?
I'm not a witch!
I'm a frog! Yay!
[Doors opening]
-Sorry about that.
-Ow.
-You really do believe
you're a witch, don't you?
-No, I'm a frog.
Oh, we're back here
at the movie.
-Yeah.
-Yes.
-There's no such thing
as witches.
I mean, real witches.
-"Real witches."
-Yeah, you know,
the kind they burn.
-Ooh.
You are so witch-ist.
-What's the matter?
-Would you like to see
where I do my witchcraft?
-I do it out of Kinkos!
-Yeah, I guess so.
-Okay.
I'll show you where to turn.
-I'm just going to stop
in this farm
and say "zah" to somebody, okay?
-Uh-oh.
Oh, this scene is going to
play hell on my hay fever!
-This is it!
-Achoo!
-Wow.
-Well, it doesn't look
very forbidding.
-Achoo!
-Ugh.
-Why should it be forbidding?
-Well, if this is where
you do your, uh,
your witchcraft.
-Achoo!
-Wow!
-Geez.
-Just what kind of witchcraft
do you do?
-Achoo!
-Oh, I witch the birds
into singing and the Sun
into coming up...
-You all right?
-I'm okay now.
-...making everything look
the way it looks.
-You're a very lovely witch.
-With your soft, downy warts.
-Come on!
-Cabin five is not on
the lake, per se.
-You know, if she had
another one of these
she could be
Melissa "Two Sheds" Strickland.
-Take a look inside.
-Just walk into
the spinning blades.
It's nice.
-Wait, you can't use "Amazing
Grace" in a devil movie!
-Go on in.
-Okay.
Ooh, lots of pig heads.
-Oh, she's a talent agent
for the Mormons.
-Your own place.
-Uh, sorry, that's the most
interesting thing
I could come up with.
-You come in here
and shut the door
and leave the world
out there somewhere.
-Do you like to turn off
the world sometimes?
-No.
No, I'm afraid
I might miss something.
-Oh, he turns off the world,
all right.
-Uh-huh.
-You do, though, don't you?
-Yes.
Sometimes.
-Mostly I just like
to turn off Canada.
-Well?
-Shall we trade clothes?
-"Well" what?
-Well, do me some witch things.
-What would you like me to do?
-Um, make me disappear.
-Yay!
-I wouldn't like to do that.
-Well, make somebody
appear, then.
-There's been
a walnut uprising.
[Giggling]
-Hello, there.
-I must agree with that.
-Is Lucinda out again?
She wandered into Jody's room
last night.
Scared him half to death.
-We'll help you look for her.
-You -- you stay here.
Stay here.
Have a good time.
-Uh, have some toast
or something.
-Poor Lucinda.
I'm the only one
she feels comfortable with,
except her doll.
-Hmm.
-It's sad.
It really is.
-Yep, really,
really, really sad.
Okay, sex then?
-What's in the chest?
-I beg your pardon?
-I'll show you.
-Well, hey!
A frog that's not deformed!
-Huh, your Maverick
is rolling down the hill.
-Woo.
The Sun just go nova out there?
-Wow.
-What's the matter?
-I can't take the pace anymore.
-I'm not sure.
Will you take me home, please?
-Sure.
-Still, that was one of
the snappiest conversations
they've had yet.
-Mm-hmm.
-Yep, obviously a herd
of grandmas came through here.
[Birds chirping]
-A-ha!
I found the murder weapon.
-Heh-heh, I'm getting way ahead
of everyone
on this scavenger hunt.
-Hmm?
Hey, a giant matchstick!
I could chew on this for months!
-Uh, I thought
of a secret Santa
gift for these people, Mike,
the book "How to
Hide a Murder Weapon."
-Okay.
-Achoo!
-Oh, not again.
-Look, here's your Allegra.
-Oh, thank -- thanks.
-There you go.
-Works fast.
-Mm-hmm.
-Mm.
Ah, thanks.
-Killer grandma got back!
-I have a feeling he's going
to lead a long, full life.
-Yeah.
-Eh, now I got to go over
and bust grandpa Walton
for raising pot.
-Oof.
Take three men to peel him
off that seat in hot weather.
-Oof.
-Unit 1, this is unit 4, over.
-I'll hang up and listen.
-Unit 1 is looking
at the radio, giggling.
-Unit 1 or unit 3, do you read?
-Whoa.
Okay, hold still!
-Where's my bike?
I reported it stolen
18 years ago!
-She...
-Aw.
-[Grunting]
-What?
What?
-Well, right about then them
Duke Boys showed up.
-Lucinda!
Lucinda!
-Guess who we saw in town!
-Just be calm
Be calm.
-Oh, I suppose you're going
to blame me for this.
-Here's his head.
You've earned it.
-I meant to ask him in for pie.
I don't know what happened!
-Well, ready to try that cider?
Hello?
-Melissa...
-Oops.
-Ew.
-Ugh.
-Oh.
-Whoa.
Hot dog, french fries,
ramen noodles.
Wow, look at him go.
-Melissa...
-Go inside with Molly.
Go ahead.
-[Mumbling]
-Go on.
Go on.
-Come on.
-This is so weird, you know.
This happened to me
on one of my first dates.
Grandma killed a guy.
-Wow.
-Huh.
-Dated the girl
for a while, though.
-Oh, good.
-Oh.
-Yeah.
-Um, Jody, that's going to
take the paint off your car.
-Yeah, yeah.
You know, a vomit-stained
Maverick was hardly a rarity
in those days.
-I'm here to tell you, nope.
[Rooster crows]
-Did she just crow?
-I think.
Gross, she's kneeling in deputy.Ew.
-Yuck.
-Huh.
Killer grandma
and locked in the barn.
Something is not right here.
-Why is that pigeon
staring at my head?
-Coo, coo, coo.
-Well, at least they didn't
chain him to a Baldwin brother.
-Ew.
-He's got that going for him.
-Wow.
-Hey, there goes Don
"The Snake" Prudhomme.
-Well, the California Bed
and Breakfast Guide
is getting an angry letter!
-Just drive carefully!
We don't want to be stopped!
-All right.
-Left the PA on.
-The keys are in the truck.
-You know, from the back,
she looks exactly
like David Cassidy.
-Don't worry about Melissa now!
Hurry up and follow me
and be careful!
-All right.
-Hello?
-They should just call Harvey
Keitel over to fix things.
-Why do you think I turned
down your road today?
-Why did you?
-Because I wanted to see
what was at the other end,
and I got lucky
because you were there.
-Huh.
I have a weird voice.
-They say in this town
that I'm a witch.
-They won't find him
until he kills again.
-She doesn't go out much
because of her face.
-Uh, me, could you
fast forward?
-Will you stay with me
a few days?
Stay here with me.
I'm lonely, Jody.
-Ew.
-I need someone to talk to.
I need someone to talk to.
To share things with,
just for a few days.
-Oh, yep.
There --
there's where I tripped up.
Yep.
-Um, I've been appointed
as your defense.
-So you done blowing groceries?
-Not going to "zah" your wayout of this one, are you, pally?
-What are they going
to do about me?
-I don't know.
-I'm going to time this pause.
One, two, three, four, five...
Wow.
Five, six, seven.
-Will you stay here
until tomorrow?
-Well, I do want
to try Grandma's waffles.
-I don't seem to
have any choice.
-Luther will unlock that
as soon as he gets back.
-They're just pausing
out of spite now.
-Yeah.
-He'll trust me not to run off?
-He'll do what I say.
-I've got pictures of him
with Mom.
-Believe me.
-Listen, that old woman...
-Just give us
until tomorrow, please.
-And what good will that do?
It won't change anything.
-Maybe I can find a way
for you to understand.
-Oh, I understand.
I understand enough to know thatif you had gone
to that sheriff 10 days ago,
that deputy
would still be alive.
-Aw, look, we don't
know he's dead.
-She killed that farmer, too,
didn't she?
Didn't she?
-Did all the actors drink
a quart of Robitussin
before shooting?
-It's wrong, Melissa.
-Luther and Molly
and you are wrong.
-We're cursed.
-No.
-We are cursed!
-Come on, we're cursed.
Please!
-You believe that.
You really do believe it.
-Yes.
-If I stay until tomorrow,
will you go away with me?
-Where?
-To the sheriff, and then
after that away from here.
Maybe back to Austin with me.
-I can never leave them.
-Anyway, I hate line dancing.
-Why?
Why, Melissa?
-What happens to my family
is my responsibility.
-And why not Luther?
It's his family.
-You saw Lucinda
this afternoon.
She barely knows Molly or Lutheror anyone exists but me.
-Well.
-I saved her.
I'm the only one
that can reach her.
-I don't understand.
-Much of anything, really.
-Then stay.
Just one more day.
-Oh, you mean, "Stay!"
-All right.
-Ladies and gentleman, the most
malleable man in the world.
-I'll find a way.
-Come on, we'll have a nice,
murder-free walk.
-You really do believe
there's some...
-Bologna left.
-Oh, yeah.
-...some devil out there.
-Oh, yes.
-I've seen his food cake.
-I suppose that makes it true.
-It is true.
-Talk quicker!
-Just like those people
in the store.
They believe you're a witch,
so it's true for them.
Well, I don't, so you're not.
-Huh.
-I'm possessed by the devil.
-Michael Eisner?
-There's no such thing.
-I learned that
in community college.
-I heard his voice!
-He sang "Lend Me a Tenor."
-No, there is no devil.
-Oh.
-Brought to you
by the National Council
for Emergency Brakes.
-Didn't there used
to be a lake here?
-Damn.
-Lesson --
Never ask Kelsey Grammer
to get your gloves
out of your car.
-Now he's handcuffed
to the meatloaf.
-I just said the steak
was a little tough.
I didn't mean to
bring everyone down.
-Ah, so you're judging us now?
-You took too many pork chops.
-I saw a robin today.
-I could put my salad fork
right in his jugular.
-Well, I'm just going to stay
through the week.
Then that's it.
-I'll go lock myself
in the barn.
Don't get up.
-Honey, I found a deputy's
badge in my stew.
Oh.
♪♪
-Hmm, I need that Scottish guy
to come over and seal
up my windows.
-It must be hard getting whale
oil anymore for these lamps.
-Check it out,
she's dressed like Ed Ames.
Skiparoo.
-Dead rubber chicken,
what is that?
-Hmm.
-Time to go be a general
in the Michigan Militia.
-Oh, I made
a terrible sock monkey.
♪♪
-My obsession with the color
brown is getting out of hand.
♪♪
-Someone is playing the cicada
in the background.
-Oh!
-Hey!
-Oh, my god.
-Ah!
-Oh, oh!
-Who is that?
-Oh.
-Hmm?
-Oh, yes.
-The editor got called out
of the room a lot I guess.
-I can't stop thinking
about that sandwich
I had the other day.
♪♪
♪ Do, do, do, Bernina
-It's the loneliest firefly
and his friends.
-Harpsichord is really
a stupid instrument.
-Oh.
-I'm sorry.
I'm in a bad mood.
-Oh, understood.
-Binding polymers and you.
-Burn the witch!
Burn the witch!
-Ah.
-Burn the witch!
-Burn the witch.
Burn the witch!
-Oh, and go Packers too...
-Burn the witch!
-...but mostly burn the witch.
-The wicked man travaileth
with pain all his days.
-Said Madeline.
-And a number of years
is hidden to the oppressor.
-Bunch of crap.
-A dreadful sound
is in his ears.
-That's Paula Cole I think.
-Yes.
-Any prosperity, the destroyer
shall come upon him.
What is it, child?
-I heard something.
-Pay attention to
the word of God.
-For he loves you, and he may
kill you if you don't.
-Yea...
-Team.
-The light of the wicked
shall be put out...
-By 10:30.
-...and the spark of his fire
shall not shine.
-Just take the old-fashioned
photo, Dad.
-The light shall be dark
in his tabernacle...
-Mm.
-And his candle shall be
put out with him.
-Listen.
-Sit back, Lucinda.
-That's Aunt Eller.
-Ooh.
-They're coming for me.
-Calm yourself.
Sit back.
-So this family has been
pausing for centuries.
It's tradition.
-The steps of his strength
shall be straightened...
-Ah, this does drag,
doesn't it?
-And his own counsel...
-Mm-hmm.
-...cast him down...
-Burn the witch!
Burn the witch!
-...for he's cast...
-Out of plastic.
-Burn the witch!
Burn the witch!
-Yes?
-Burn the witch!
Burn the witch!
-...for he's cast into a...
-Yeah.
-...net...
-And it just goes
on from there.
-Oh.
Oh, that's right.
I called a service to come
around and burn my witch.
-What is it, David?
-It's people saying,
"Burn the witch."
Are you deaf?
-Burn the witch!
Burn the witch!
-Papa, what is it?
-People saying,
"Burn the witch."
Do you have any
deductive powers at all?
-I don't know yet.
-Burn the witch!
-Take your mother to the back
of the house...
-Work her over.
-And I'll see
what this is about.
-Burn the witch!
Burn the witch!
-It's pretty casual.
It's kind of like
a Lake Wobegon witch burning.
-Burn the witch!
Burn the witch!
-Burn the witch.
-Say, are you guys
burning witches?
Can I come?
-Big Hoss has lost some weight.
-Uh, we was out burning,
uh, uh, uh, uh... You tell him.
-Well, it seems
kind of silly now.
-Good evening, Mr. Keitel.
-Mr. Strickland.
-You've been hitting
the booze again.
-What can I do for you?
-Um, Mrs. Lucaster lost
her young one tonight,
only 3 years old.
-Left her at Gymboree.
-I'm sorry to hear that.
-Kester Hagan here lost three
head of cow tonight,
and his wife is down sick.
-Hmm.
-I'm sorry.
-And my souffle fell today.
-It's a plague.
-I understand.
-Plague.
-The plague has hit near
everybody here,
David Strickland,
but it ain't hit you.
Now, how do you explain that?
-Well, I don't comb my hair
with rat bones.
-I can only assume...
-That I'm Franz Schubert.
-...that it's God's will.
-Don't talk to us about God,
David Strickland.
There's a witch in that house,
and we aim to have her.
-There is no witch
in that house.
-Well, my daughter
is kind of a witch,
but other than that, no witches.
-Go on home!
-We'll not go home until we get
what we come for.
Your daughter is a witch,
and she's put a hex on us!
-That's a damn fool thing
to say, Mr. Keitel.
Go on home.
-Ah, look at them go.
Run, you yellow-belly...
Oh, you're not.
-I'll talk to you tomorrow down
at Ben Proctor's store.
-There will be no talk.
We'll have the witch.
-Over my dead body!
-Uh-oh.
-So be it.
-Hmm.
-Come on.
-Smooth, Strickland.
-Lucinda, run!
Run!
-Oh, take my daughter, but
spare my commemorative plates!
-Oh, run, Lucinda, no!
-Ah!
Oh!
[Doors closing]
[Doors continue closing]
-[Speaking gibberish]
-Ah!
-Hey, hey, who are you?
Servo, stop it!
What are you doing?
Servo, heaven's sake!
-Bum, bum, buh, bum, bum,
dum, dum, hi, Mike.
What are you... What?
Grandma, darn it, Grandma!
Stop!
Now I told you, "No."
Jeez, I'm sorry, Mike.
-Wait a minute.
This is your grandma?
-It sure is, Mike.
Isn't she spry?
-When did you
get a grandma?
Ow, stay away.
-I have two grandmas, Mike.
I always have.
The other one doesn't
kill people though.
This one does.
That's how I tell them apart.
Ah, Grandma, down.
-Hey, hey.
-Down, Grandma.
-Oh, I guess it's okay.
I mean, couldn't you get her
a TV or something?
-Hold on a second.
What's that, Grandma?
Big, slow, tempting target?
Oh, believe me.
I know, but you just can't,
okay?
Well, I'll tell you what, Mike.
I'm just going to leave you
two alone
to start all over
with each other.
All right?
-No, Servo, don't.
-Oh, she's full of stories,
Mike!
Have a good time!
-Hey, hey, get away from me.
We'll be right back.
Back off, lady.
What?
I'm sorry.
I didn't catch that.
What?
Ow, ow, hey, lady, stop it!
Stop it!
Stop!
Now back down, down, down!
♪♪
-Let go!
You're hurting me!
Let go of me!
-Ah, don't these people
have butter to churn
or taffy to pull,
prairie leagues to form?
-Something.
-Get off of me, no!
Please don't tie me up!
No, please stop!
-Please let me go!
-Quit whining.
-No, no, no, no!
-Help me!
Let me down from here!
-Oh, Neil Young.
-Oh, no, you're
making a mistake!
Help me!
Help me, Melissa!
-Hey, you been working out?
-Oh, no!
-You know, maybe if
the Amish used buttons,
they wouldn't be so irrational.
-No, no!
-Please, you're hurting me,
please!
-No!
-Burn the witch.
-Yeah, that's the plan, Amos.
-Ah!
-Burn the witch.
-No!
Burn the witch.
-Oh, this is so gauche.
-Molly, please help me.
-Burn the witch.
-Please don't do this.
Burn the witch.
♪ Amazing grace
-Take her down!
♪ How sweet the sound
-Help!
Somebody help!
Oh, damn you!
-Every week, we do this!
♪ That saved a wretch like me
-Somebody, anybody,
I beg of you, anybody!
Oh, my God, no.
-♪ This song is
in the public domain ♪
♪ That's why we used it twice
-Will you save her?
I say again.
Would you save the witch?
-Shall I wrap her up for you?
-Yes, save her.
-You been hitting the booze?
-Will you accept me
as your master?
-And go fetch?
-Yes, yes.
-Hold up your hand.
-Let me stamp it.
-Now, put out the fire.
-Hmm.
-Caleb, what kind of charcoal
did you use?
-Must have got a hold
of a wet witch.
-You have asked for death...
-Ooh.
-...and you shall have it!
May your livestock
sicken and die!
-Moo, oh.
-May your crops rot
on the ground!
-Happened already.
-May your houses be infested
with snakes and scorpions!
-Houses?
You have houses?
-And may your firstborn be
deformed as pigs and toads!
-May your tomatoes
be flavorless!
-Ah!
-Let's burn some Beatles
records instead!
[Crowd yelling]
-I do okay with the curses?
I'm open to criticism.
♪♪
♪ Do, do, do, do, do, do
-Ooh, ouch, you're
still hot, ow.
-You know what?
Those villages really
burn me up. Ha, he, heh, heh.
It's good that I can laugh, oh.
-Who are you?
-I am friend and companion
of the night.
I rejoice in spilled blood
and the baying of dogs.
-Oh.
-Ew.
-I wander among
shades and tombs.
I am Gorgo and Mormo
of the thousand-faced moon.
-But call me Sue.
-What would you have of me?
-I ask that you know me
when I return.
I will return.
-Oh, hold on.
I'm getting a call
from Margot Adler.
-Um, Gorgo, Mormo, you want
to help me with this knot?
-This is the weirdest
"Big Valley" ever.
-Uh, I wish I brought a change
of pants on this trip.
They're all crunchy.
-Oh, what is
keeping me up tonight?
I had a cup of tea at dinner.
Oh, right,
Grandma mutilated a cop!
That would do it.
-Well, I'm going to go puke
on the Maverick.
-Okay, everyone,
hold on just a second.
I just want to see
if he gets his shoes on, yes,
yes, great,
glad they showed that to us.
-God, where did they find
the 590-watt light bulb.
-I actually need
something meat hooked.
I'm going to go see
if Grandma is up.
[Footsteps]
-Yep, I still think he has
those shoes on, you guys.
I can hear them.
-Good.
-Yeah, good.
-I'm going to keep my eye
on that situation.
-Thanks, Mike.
-I'll let you know.
-Okay.
-Oh, hey, look!
Grannies do swing on
the outhouse door
without their nighties!
-Ah, he's got the shoes
on here.
This is good, yeah.
A little bit of redundancy
on the shoes is good, Mike.
I'm going to back
you up on this.
-Thanks.
You know, unless there is
a change,
I think we can just assume he's
wearing the shoes from now on.
-Yeah, yeah, good.
-Maybe this was
once fast-paced,
and someone spilled a Grape Nehion it, and it got all gummy.
-Maybe.
-I realized we hadn't had
a stuttering conversation
for several hours.
-Hmm?
-He rejoices in spilled blood
and the baying of dogs.
-Marilyn Manson?
-He is Gorgo and Mormo.
-And Joe.
-Stop it.
-If you can hang on a sec,
I'm about to say something.
-Jody, you turned down
the road yesterday
because you wanted to see
what was at the other end.
-Just like that chicken.
-Well, now you've seen it,
but you won't believe it.
-I can't.
-Not can't, won't.
-Ah.
-You won't believe in the devil
because you're afraid if you
believe in him, he'll be real.
-It's like when you wouldn't
believe in peanut butter.
-He is real.
I heard him.
I felt him inside me.
-That was acid reflux.
-It's not true.
-Face it.
-Aw.
-I've had to.
Do you think I like it?
Do you think I've enjoyed
all these years
with the devil's spirit
inside me?
-Sure, we've had some laughs.
-It happened, Jody,
just like in your dream.
-That dream was coincidence.
-Is it a coincidence
that I know
they sang a hymn in your dream.
The good Christians sang
a good Christian song
while they were
burning my sister.
-And they didn't even have
a youth-horn section.
-♪ Amazing grace
-♪ And chalk
-♪ How sweet the sound
♪ That saved a wretch like me
♪ Public domain
We don't have to pay anyone ♪
♪ Ha, ha, ha, ha
-What are you doing to me?
-It's that witchcraft,
wicked witchcraft!
-Why is it so important that I
believe in this devil of yours?
-Well, I get
a commission, so...
-Because you can save me.
I've got a sickness
in me, Jody.
-I've got occasional
devil worship.
-You can free me from it
but not unless you
believe it exists.
-Aren't there any Jesuits
in the phone book?
Come on.
-How can I help you?
-What can I, a single puss, do?
-By believing what
I've told you...
-Mm-hmm.
-...and what I'm going
to tell you...
-Let me pause to drench
my next line in meaning.
-I want to help you.
-But I'm really busy right now.
-I love you.
-And I've grown awfully fond
of your grandma.
-May I touch your sideburn?
-Then hear the rest of it.
-I want to help you.
-Consarn it, breaking up my
dagnabbit contract with Satan!
-Oh, wow, Poopdeck Pappy
getting all upset here.
-They turned me down
for that policy!
They said it couldn't happen!
-I want, want, want,
want, want, want to help you.
-No!
-Ha ha, I told you
I could take you, you pansies!
I could take the whole family!
-Wow.
♪♪
-I can't believe I have
to wash Satan's towels.
-Melissa...
-Crossroads seem
to come and go.
-...if all this were true,
that would make you
127 years old.
-Yes.
-Man, she's getting into
Strom Thurmond country.
-Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding, that's the train
going through the pause.
-Is it still the same pause,
or is it
technically a sub-pause?
-Even if it were true,
I'd love you anyway.
-I mean, I'd put you
in a home, but...
-Ugh.
-Hey, John Quincy Adams.
-Lucinda!
-Wow.
-Run, Jody.
-Grandma used to work
for the LAPD.
-Witch, oh.
-Whoops.
-Oh, no!
-Be gone, witch!
Burn!
-Oh, and Grandma
had just gotten a job
as a greeter at Walmart.
-Oh!
♪ Amazing grace
-Hey, Mike, what were you guys
doing there in the '70s...
-Yeah.
-...making witch movies,
inhaling huge clouds
of marijuana...
-What's your deal?
-...big ugly flared pants on.
-We had to do something.
♪ That saved a wretch like me
-Melissa, come on!
-Oh, she'll be fine!
Come on!
♪ I once was lost
-You know,
when you're that age,
you're just ready
to go right up.
The slightest spark
can get it going.
Let me tell you.
♪ Was blind but now I see
-Aw, now she's
Melissa Noshed Strickland.
-Man, never let Edie Sedgwick
borrow your lake cabin.
♪ Amazing grace
-I've done it, no good.
-Oh, Grandma must have exploded
or something.
-Man.
♪ How sweet the sound
♪ That saved a wretch like me
-Grandma's flash-paper bathrobe
turned out to be a mistake.
♪ I once was lost
-Oh, if the septic tank
goes up, we're all in trouble.
♪ But now I am found
♪ Was blind
-In the wake of the tragedy,
the town
built a better
grandma, stronger,
with a steel frame
and a sprinkler system.
[Dove cooing]
-Now I just have to watch out
for my other grandma.
She's really crazy.
-Oh, oh, oh, you think
I want to do saliva?
Is that why you did that?
Ugh.
-Hmm, not worth it, sorry,
I had fun though.
See you.
-Can you not French my daughter
during breakfast?
-Goodbye, sir.
Thank you for trusting me now.
I'll keep my word.
-I'll tell no one of your
back-sweat problem.
-Well, let's lock you back
in the barn.
-I'll walk out to the car
with you.
-Could you drop me off
at Tanglewood?
I'm conducting Mahler's
10th this weekend.
-Get the lens more.
We need more light, more!
-I see Grandma
behind that tree.
You might want to make
a run for it.
-I just wanted to ask you while
we're away from all the others,
Do you think we're weird at all?
-It's all true, you know,
everything she told you.
-I'm sorry, sir.
I can't believe that,
and I can't believe she's
possessed by the devil either.
-I suppose not.
-Whatever.
-Be careful.
Goodbye, Jody.
-Goodbye, sir.
-Oh, and don't join
Al Pacino's law firm.
Heh- heh
Whew.
-May the dark one hold
your soul in his clutch --
I mean, safe trip.
-Yo.
-Man, nice kid, eh,
the bomb should go off
in a couple of minutes.
♪♪
-Ah, Fritz Kreisler used
to wear
a striped shirt like that.
-Hmm, oh, I've got so many
walnut husks in my teeth.
-Well, I should say goodbye
to the fish I suppose.
-Where the heck is
that village smithy?
-I am hungry,
but I can't go back
to the grocery store
after that "zah" incident.
♪♪
-Wow, look at the smoke.
Everybody must be
burning their grandmas today.
♪♪
-Hey, I ran out of gas.
Heh-heh.
I'm kind of a wolfwhen I'm alone with myself, yep.
-Hey, the odometer
is all sixes.
♪♪
-Wait a minute.
Where is my immortal soul?
Crap, I left it back
at the farm.
-Oh, we're back
at the beginning.
This film is a Mobius strip.
-Yeah.
♪♪
-My fish moved and different
leave a forwarding address.
-See, I don't get
how they build this
as a rollicking musical.
-No.
-The only known shots
of bigfoot in a T-shirt.
-Come.
Sit in the crotch,
you know, the tree.
-Raw.
-I love you, Melissa.
-Almost as much as I love
wide-wale corduroys.
-It doesn't matter that
the devil is in your soul.
-Oh, look familiar, Mike?
-Hey.
-I love you.
-Uh, are you blowing me off,
or is this just
one of our pauses?
-Our next pause is going
to be this big.
-Ready?
Wrestle!
♪♪
-The devil just happens
to be peeking out of
her mouth right now.
-Hey, get out of there!
-Well, the dates are easy
without Grandma
clubbing him to death.
♪♪
-Huh?
Man, I thought
I was an operator.
-He's fast.
-Whoa.
-You know, my mom used
to have a little saying.
It's just as easy
to fall in love
with a woman who's
not possessed by the devil.
-Mm-hmm.
-Right.
-I have one chest hair.
-Okay, kids,
the picnic is this way.
What?
Ah!
-Ah!
-You freed me.
-I've turned into Gloria Stuart
at last.
-I love you, Melissa.
-Oh.
-I do love you.
-But why are you
sanding my shoulder?
-Oh, you seem to have some sort
of tarp on your hand.
-You see, you're going to have
to expect a little of this
when your bride is Satan.
-Oh, yeah, I should know.
-What's wrong?
-Your face.
-Well, what's wrong
with my face?
-Oh, nothing if you
like Eubie Blake.
-Oh, my God.
-I've become Sigourney Weaver.
-He cheated me.
He never told me.
-Man, if you can't
trust the devil.
-Yeah.
-Jody, I -- I'm going to die.
-No.
-You're 127 years young.
-There's a way.
-No.
-Jody, not that way.
-What would you have of me?
-Don't let her die.
I love her.
-Whoa, boy, no, I don't.
-Will you accept me
as your master?
-Yes.
-No, no.
-Then save her.
-Morally save her.
-Hit him.
-Quickly now, save her.
-Well, I guess that's what
I was calling you for, devil.
♪♪
-Oh.
-I should have asked the devil
to throw
in some other modifications
while I was at it.
♪♪
-Good, so we're both
in the clutches of the devil
because you wanted seconds.
-And they drift apart
after 3 weeks.
-Uh, we're going to have
illiterate jackals
in 9 months, you know.
-This is a good pause
we're having, eh?
-Yeah, I'm guessing this guy
is going to be
a fairly minor soldier
in the devil's army.
-Yeah, probably have a tiny
picture in hell's newsletter.
-Yeah.
-Well, they better book
a hall in hell
for their unholy wedding.
It's like a year wait.
-Yep.
-Oh, I don't know.
I don't trust this, Mike.
I think this is just
the longest pause yet.
-Okay.
-So in the end,
Satan wins I guess.
-Yep, pretty much
a shutout for Satan.
-Yep.
-Ah, the devil!
-Oh, look out!
-Ah!
-Let's get out of here.
♪♪
[Doors closing]
-Sweet deal, hey, hey, Mike,
I just sold myself to Satan.
-Oh, you did?
-Uh, yeah, so I'm probably
going to have lots
of unfathomable
worldly power real soon,
and I thought I'd give you
the heads-up on that.
-Oh, that's real thoughtful
of you.
Thanks, Crow.
-Yep, got a contract
right here from Satan.
-Let me see that.
-Shall take possession
of his mortal soul,
yeah, that all scans.
Oh, uh, but look at this,
a little mistake here.
It looks like you sold your soulto Stan, not Satan.
-Huh.
-Yeah.
-Well, there's a number there.
Would you mind
calling it please?
-Oh, yeah, that's a good idea.
-Wow.
-Yeah, see this?
This isn't even the area code
for hell, so...
-Ah.
-Yep.
-Yellow, Stan Johnson?
-Ah, see, there you go.
Hi, uh, Stan, this is,
uh, Mike Nelson.
You're not by any chance
the Devil, are you?
-Uh, nope.
I'm a CPA
and investment consultant.
-Damn.
-Ah, yeah.
Hey, I'm calling on behalf
of Crow T. Robot.
-Oh, right, little skinny
gold guy, kind of bug-eyed?
Sure.
-Got it.
-Yeah, that's the guy.
Hey, did you buy his soul?
-Yes, I did.
I manage a well-balanced
portfolio of souls.
They can be very high-yield.
-Um, um, Stan, this is Crow.
When can I get my soul back?
Is that possible or...
-Oh, I'm sorry.
I resold your soul
already to Citicorp
in a big block of souls.
-Ah, man, I am going to have
to make so many phone calls
go get my soul back.
-Oh, man.
Oh, and Pearl's babysitter
is calling.
-Phew.
-Hello?
-Be with you in a minute.
-Almost finished story time,
then everyone goes to sleep.
-Um, can I come out now?
-Shush!
Bad dog!
Go to sleep!
-Okay.
-Now, where was I, Brian?
-Oh, uh, the tall fellow
was repeatedly refusing
to ingest
green eggs and ham.
The short fellow was
bizarrely insistent upon it.
-Yes, very good.
-Yeah.
-"I will not eat them
in a plane.
I will not eat them on a train."-"On a train," right.
You know, why doesn't
he just leave him alone?
He has pointedly made his
refusal to eat this dish clear.
The mere hypothetical changing
of a location
is irrelevant and tedious,
and --
and that Sam I Am is so bloody
repetitive, I could scream!
-Are we a little cranky, Brian?
-No, madam.
I am overtired,
so I shall turn in now,
so if you wouldn't mind,
please, my blankie,
my nookie, and my friend.
Ah, thank you kindly.
Good morrow to you.
-Nighty night.
-Well, now, me, uh,
I'd definitely
eat them on a train.
There's no doubt about that.
-Quiet! No bark!
-It'd be delicious on a train,
but a plane,
I'd have to think about a plane.
Maybe substitute bacon for ham.
That sounds kind of nice,
and we could have a...
Oh, boy.
-No bark!
-I'm not barking.
I was just talking.
Ooh!
I'm commenting on the story!
There's no barking involved
at all!
-No!
No bark!
-Ow!
-No, I'm not sure
you see my point.
Here, it's like this.
Rather than barking,
as you assumed,
I was actually...
Oh, come on!
I'm --I'm talking, not...
Oh!
-No!
-Ow!
-No bark!
I'm not barking!
I'm... Ow...
-Bad dog!
-...articulating, and...
Oh, jeez!
Ow, ow!
-Bad, dog!
-Ow, stop it!
♪♪
-This is where the fish
lives.